http://www.fieldtripfactory.com/privacy

Contact us
HomeField Trip IdeasGrades PreK - 2 Grades 3 and UpOnline ProgramsCanadaResourcesSocial CommunityPrivacyNewsletter Sign-UpBlogAbout UsContact UsOur SponsorsSponsor ListBecome a Sponsor
Register
Login
Field Trip Factory Privacy Policy
FTF Does Not Sell Your Contact Information
While using this site, you may choose to submit organizational and/or personal information via email or online forms. FTF will use this information to process your requests. FTF will not intentionally sell your personal information to third parties. FTF only discloses information as required by law and in support of our partner organizations by following CAN-SPAM Act guidelines.
Statistical Data
FTF uses industry standard reporting programs to collect data about visitor traffic to our site. FTF  does not attempt to personally identify visitors unless using user-provided information via site log-in to help personalize your experience. FTF collects general data to analyze in aggregate to determine trends and improve our website and programs. Examples of the types of data FTF routinely collects:
Internet address of computer
Browser type
Referring web page
Program pages visited
Date, time & duration of visit
Cookies
FieldTripFactory.com, like most internet sites, leverages the use of cookies (bits of data passed by your browser to our site). Example:  FieldTripFactory.com uses cookies (active only during your session) to remember password and menu settings regarding your personal preferences. To maintain the optimum user experience, Field Trip Factory recommends enabling cookies in your browser settings for FieldTripFactory.com.  Turning-off cookie access for FieldTripFactory.com via your browser settings will result in a failure to log-in and access other personalized data on our website.
Security
Field Trip Factory utilizes appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, to assist in maintaining data security, and to assist in correctly using the information we collect online. We do not intentionally release personal information gleaned from these programs to others, except as required by law.
Security Precautions You Should Take
Although we make every effort to secure our website, Field Trip Factory cannot guarantee privacy of online communications. Please use discretion in providing information via open forums on the Web. FTF recommends exiting the site and closing your browser when finished with your visits. Otherwise, the next person to use the same computer may have access to information you have provided.
Protecting Children's Privacy
Field Trip Factory recognizes that parents and educators may view our website in conjunction with their children or students. If FTF learns that a child under age 13 has provided personally identifiable information to our sites, FTF will promptly remove this from our files. For more on children's privacy rights, read about the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act at the FTC's website.  Field Trip Factory obtains applicable photographic release for permission to use all imagery on our website.
Please direct any questions on our Privacy Policy to info@FieldTripFactory.com
